A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - Malone, NY, 1008.15/Roll823A, 823C; (11) (Box 7)
    - Governor shakes hands with Trooper F.L. Boehl, State Police, Malone, NY (Roll 823C, Frame 10)
    - Governor with Roy Hall, Mrs. Roy Hall and Mrs. Bligh Dodds of Governor, NY (Roll 823C, Frame 4)
  - Saranac Lake, NY, 1008.15/Roll823D; (10) (Box 7)
    - At Saranac Lake Airport, 1008.15/Roll823D (Box 7)
      - Governor and Mayor Robert Peacock of Lake Placid, NY (Roll 823, Frame 1)
      - Governor with Avery Rockefeller at Saranac Lake Airport (Roll 823, Frame 2)
      - Governor with Mr. and Mrs. Donald Tyler of Hannibal, NY and their daughter Dorothy 2 (Roll 823, Frame 3-4)
      - at Uhilein-Chonell Potato Farm and Governor in Farm Wagon with Dr. Edward Jones (left) Commissioner Don Wickham also (Roll 823, Frame 4-8)
      - Governor and sign made by Mrs. Edward Jones (Roll 823, Frame 9-12)
  - Lake Placid, NY, 1008.15/Roll823E-823F (Box 7)
    - At Lake Placid (Box 7)
      - Governor at Uhilein Farm House (Roll 823E, Frame 1)
      - With Mr. and Mrs. Uhilein Farm House (Roll 823E, Frame 2)
      - Governor speaking at reception at Uhilein Farm House. Mr. and Mrs. Uhilein in picture (Roll 823E, Frame 3)
      - Governor with Sister Mary Michele (Roll 823E, Frame 4-5)
      - Group with Governor (Roll 823E, Frame 6)
      - Governor with Uhilein (Roll 823E, Frame 7)
      - blank (Roll 823E, Frame 8-9)
      - at Lake Placid Parade (Roll 823E, Frame 10)
      - Governor rides convertible (Roll 823E, Frame 11)
    - Village Parking Lot Rally (Box 7)
      - with members of Housewives for Rockefeller group (Roll 823F, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor greets Scott Steffens and Rev James S Steffens of East Northport, LI (Roll 823F, Frame 3)
      - Governor with Mrs. Robert L Colby (Roll 823F, Frame 4)
      - Governor speaks at Lake Placid Rally (Roll 823F, Frame 5)
      - Governor with Lake Placid Hospital sign (Roll 823F, Frame 6-7)
      - Governor with Mrs. Florence Stuntz (Roll 823F, Frame 8-9)
  - Sherry Armbruster, Carol Collins, Linda Cumbo, 1966 August 23; 1008.15/1773 (Box 7)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1966 August 24 (Box 7)
    - Governor arrives at Buffalo Airport - Shirlee J Winters & Julie Schulze (Roll 824A, Frame 1)
    - Beckinghausen - Cheektowaga, NY (Roll 824A, Frame 2)
    - Governor with Daniel A Roblin Jr - President of Roblin Steel Corp. and Paul Ivanier - President of Sivaco Wire & Nail Co. as they announced new industrial plant for area (Roll 824A, Frame 3-4)
    - Governor leaves bus at Erie County Fair Grounds (Roll 824A, Frame 6-7)
    - Governor greets admirers at Erie County Fair (Roll 824A, Frame 8-9)
    - Governor with Mr. and Mrs. Theodore Willard - autographs her arm cast (Roll 824A, Frame 10)
    - Governor surrounded by admirers at Fair (Roll 824A, Frame 11-12)
    - At Erie County Fair (Roll 824B)
      - Mrs. Bruce J Moden and her children Lind 2 y/o, Nancy 3 y/o, Valerie 4 y/o (Roll 824B, Frame 1)
      - Governor with Mrs. William Magavern (Roll 824B, Frame 2-3)
      - her children Lydia 19m/o and Mary 4 1/2 y/o (Roll 824B, Frame 4)
      - Governor talks to Mrs. Jane Fowler at Taffy Stand (Roll 824B, Frame 5)
      - Governor with Mrs. Dorothy Stopak (Roll 824B, Frame 6)
      - Governor with cotton candy at booth of Wilber L. Leworthy, he is giving a bite of candy to Shirlee J Winters (Roll 824B, Frame 7)
      - Group at WBEN-TV interview (Roll 824B, Frame 8)
      - Governor autographs stuffed animal of Wander Wilson (Roll 824B, Frame 9)
      - Governor at Buffalo Courier express hole in one booth (Roll 824B, Frame 10-12)
    - Governor with Mrs. Ida Laughing (Niagara Falls, NY) and her daughter Brenda, 9 y/o, who later presented gift to Governor (Roll 824C, Frame 1)
    - Governor inside NYS. Trailer (Roll 824C, Frame 2)
    - Bishop Brzana of Buffalo makes presentation of plaque to Governor (Roll 824C, Frame 4)
    - Governor at Polish-Millian Luncheon, big group not identified (Roll 824C, Frame 5)
    - Governor with Bishop Brzana and Henery J. Osinski, send best of 4 or 5 to Jack Lyons for Polish weekly paper (Roll 824C, Frame 6-10)
    - Governor with clown - Charlie Cheer (Roll 824D, Frame 1)
    - Governor and sulky and "Charity Song" trotter owned by Willard Jensen, he rode sulky round track at Erie County Fair (Roll 824D, Frame 2-7)
  - Pike, NY, Wyoming County Fair, 1008.15/Roll824E-F (Box 7)
    - At Wyoming County Fair (Box 7)
      - Governor greets Mrs. Smith McTyre (Roll 824D, Frame 8)
      - Governor with Sheriff Dalton Carney and Jane Cook (Wyoming county Fair Queen) (Roll 824D, Frame 9)
      - At Wyoming county Fair, Governor rides horse (Roll 824D, Frame 10-11)
      - Governor with family of Congressman Barber Conable this film given to Bill Wilt who will mail to NY City Wyoming. County Bureau. Rochester Times Union Democrat Chronicle (Roll 824D, Frame 12)
    - Wyoming County Fair (Roll 824E)
      - Sheriff Dalton Carney with some of his family (Roll 824E, Frame 1)
      - Sheriff Carney and more of his family (Roll 824E, Frame 2)
      - Governor with Assemblyman Frank Walkley and his family (Roll 824E, Frame 3)
      - Governor with John Emerling of Perry, NY and his prize winning cow (Roll 824E, Frame 4-5)
      - Governor with 8 y/o Darlene Shirley Martin of Perry, NY (Roll 824E, Frame 6-7)
      - Governor at Wyoming County Republican booth at fair (Roll 824E, Frame 8-10)
      - Governor with Motorola Arcade NY officials-Paul Knesel - Public relations, Franklin Park, Il W.O. Bruyere - Plant Manager 400 W. Main St, Arcade, NY (Roll 824E, Frame 11)
    - Governor tastes maple syrup product. Mrs. Leo W. George, Route 77, Strykersville, NY (Roll 824F, Frame 1)
    - Les Slote eats com (Roll 824F, Frame 2)
    - Governor eats com at left is Fair Manager, Donald Robinson of Silver Springs, NY (Roll 824F, Frame 3)
    - Miss Randa Crosby of Pike NY, and Mrs. Caroline Beardsly Jr of Pike NY, give Governor ice cream at Firemen's Auxiliary and American Legion Auxiliary booth. (Roll 824F, Frame 4-5)
    - Governor gets hat from Nelson from Mrs. Benson Bliemeister, 821 Schultz Rd, Elma, NY (Roll 824F, Frame 6)
    - at motel stop Orangeville, NY (Roll 824, Frame 10F)
    - Governor with Mr. and Mrs. Andrew Heyburn of Warsaw, NY (Roll 824F, Frame 11)
  - Alexander, NY, 1008.15/Roll824G; (6) (Box 7)
    - Governor arrives at Fireman's Hall, Alexander, NY for Genesee Republican dinner (Roll 824G, Frame 1)
    - with members of Alexander High School Band (Roll 824G, Frame 2)
    - N.G. possible fogged (Roll 824G, Frame 3)
    - Governor with members of the Alexander NY Fire Department Auxiliary who prepared dinner (Roll 824G, Frame 4-5)
    - Governor speaks at dinner (Roll 824G, Frame 6)
    - Governor with Miss Mary R Wright - Innkeeper at Treadway Inn Batavia, NY (Roll 824G, Frame 7)
  - Dansville, NY, 1966 August 25; 1008.15/Roll825A; (11) (Box 7)
    - Governor arrives at Brae Burn Recreation Center, Dansville, NY by helicopter for Livingston County Republican Breakfast (Roll 825A, Frame 1-2)
    - Governor with members of Dansville High School Band (Roll 825A, Frame 3)
    - Governor greets your Republicans (Roll 825A, Frame 4)
    - Governor speaks at Livingston County Breakfast (Roll 825A, Frame 5-6)
    - Governor greets Mrs. Clement Schuster of Dansville, NY (Roll 825A, Frame 7)
    - Governor with group of Young Republicans (Roll 825A, Frame 8)
    - sculptor and elephant at Dansville (Roll 825A, Frame 9-10)
    - Governor with Kelly and family (Roll 825A, Frame 11)
    - Governor with Mrs. Bruce Macintyre of Casey Rd, Caledonis, NY and sculptured elephant made by town of York Republican Client (Roll 825A, Frame 12)
  - Hornell, New York, 1008.15/Roll825B-825C (Box 7)
    - At Rally Union Park (Roll 825B)
      - Governor arrives for Rally at Union Park, Hornell (Roll 825B, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor speaking (Roll 825B, Frame 3)
      - Governor with key presented by Mayor Harold Crandall of Hornell (Roll 825B, Frame 4)
      - at right (man is white jacket) Charles Henderson (Roll 825B, Frame 5)
      - Governor presents flag to Tom McCarthy, (335 Charles St, Hornell) (Roll 825B, Frame 6)
      - Governor in crowd at Hornell (Roll 825B, Frame 7)
      - Governor with 83 y/o Albert Fawcett of Canastraga, NY (Roll 825B, Frame 8)
      - Governor with TARS - Dick Snowden (of Hornell) is presenting a tray, others in photograph are Kevin Clark, Steven Lyke and Michael Snowden (Roll 825B, Frame 9-10)
    - Governor is given home made by "plane" by Tim Quillin (of Hornell) (Roll 825C, Frame 1)
    - Governor at St. James Hospital, Hornell - see construction. With Governor are Sister Mary Rene and Sister Mary Scholastica (Roll 825C, Frame 2-3)
    - Governor with youngster at hospital (Roll 825C, Frame 4-5)
    - At Hornell Senior High School (Roll 825C)
      - Governor Arrives at High school (Roll 825C, Frame 6)
      - Governor speaking (Roll 825C, Frame 7)
      - School Board President Ted Beyer makes presentation to Governor (Roll 825C, Frame 8)
      - Governor presents state flag to Junior High School Principal, Paul Toth of Hornell, NY (Roll 825C, Frame 9)
      - Governor visits Bethesda Community Hospital (Roll 825C, Frame 10-12)
  - Bath, NY, 1008.15/Roll825D-825E (Box 7)
    - untitled, 1008.15/Roll825D; (10)
    - untitled, 1008.15/Roll825E; (11) (Box 7)
    - Governor on old fire truck driven by Mayor John Langerdorfer of Bath, NY and Struben County Fair (Roll 825D, Frame 1-5)
    - Governor watches Haverling Central School Band march passed stand (Roll 825D, Frame 6)
    - Governor presents state flag to Kathy Eister and Luther Hoffman - Director of Haverling Central School Band. (Roll 825D, Frame 7-8)
    - Governor with Young Republican group? At Fair (Roll 825D, Frame 9)
    - Governor greets two y/o Mac Tillman, son of Mrs. Myron Tillman of Bath, NY (Roll 825D, Frame 10)
    - Steuben County Fair (Box 7)
      - Governor with Richard Drinkard (of Elmira, NY) (Roll 825E, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor buys candy from Mrs. Donna Englert (of Bath NY) (Roll 825E, Frame 3)
      - Governor at Steuben County Republican Booth at Fair (Roll 825E, Frame 5-6)
      - Governor with News Director, Dan Phillips and Program Director Dean Close of Radio Station WWHG of Hornell, NY (Roll 825E, Frame 7)
      - Governor with Mr. and Mrs. Bertrand Austin (of Buffalo, NY) and their children Bruce and Tracey (Roll 825E, Frame 8)
      - Governor speaks at picnic of Town Highway Superintendent and town officer at Bath, NY (Roll 825E, Frame 9)
      - Governor with children of Anthony Maititra, Moonlight Restaurant, Bath NY (Roll 825E, Frame 10-12)
  - Watkins Glen, NY, 1008.15/Roll825F; (7) (Box 7)
    - At Schuyler County Republican Barbeque, Chute Park, Watkins Glen, NY (Roll 825F, Frame 1)
    - Governor leans over table to greet guests (Roll 825F, Frame 3-4)
    - Governor with Mrs. Mildred Wolcott (Watkins Glen, NY) Mrs. Fred Wiltse (Watkins Glen, NY) Miss Susan Smith (Trumansburg, NY) who were unable to find table space at the barbeque (Roll 825F, Frame 5)
    - Governor speaks (Roll 825F, Frame 7)
    - Crowd at barbeque listen to Governor (Roll 825F, Frame 8-9)
    - Governor with District Attorney William Allison and Mrs. Allison (Roll 825F, Frame 10)
  - Penn Yan, NY, 1008.15/Roll825G; (12) (Box 7)
  - Greenwich, NY, 1966 August 26; 1008.15/Roll826A; (10) (Box 7)
    - unidentified (Roll 826A, Frame 1)
    - Governor with James Robert Campbell (he is man in background next to boy) (Roll 826A, Frame 2)
    - Governor with Howard Cleveland and Children (Roll 826A, Frame 3)
    - Governor at Red Cross Booth (Roll 826A, Frame 4-5)
    - Governor with 13 year old Cynthia Kimball and heifer calf (Roll 826A, Frame 6)
    - Governor at Republican Booth (Roll 826A, Frame 7)
    - Governor with Sheriff (Roll 826A, Frame 10)
    - Governor is congratulated by Mayor & Mrs. Charles Dolan of Greenwich, NY as he visited Democratic Booth at Fair. Other person is Mrs. Marjorie Reed of Greenwich, NY (who may show in picture) (Roll 826A, Frame 11)
  - Washington County Fair, 1008.15/Roll826B; (10) (Box 7)
    - Governor at Maple Syrup Booth of Mrs. Kay Eggleston and her son, George (Roll 826B, Frame 1)
    - Governor with Miss Norma Allen, Dairy Queen after she presented Dairy Industries of Washington county Award (Roll 826B, Frame 2)
    - Governor speaks at Fair, (pictures in which children are in foreground to be sent to R. C. Saunders) (Roll 826B, Frame 3-7)
    - Governor with David Mocher, he is future farmer (Roll 826B, Frame 8)
    - Governor signs autographs (Roll 826B, Frame 10)
    - Three y/o Jay Howlett (Roll 826B, Frame 11)
    - Son of Mrs. Linda Howlett with Governor at end of Radio Interview (Roll 826B, Frame 12)
  - Rhinebeck. NY, 1008.15/Roll826C-826D; (13) (Box 7)
    - At Duchess County Fair (Roll 826C)
      - Governor arrives at Poughkeepsie Airport (Roll 826C, Frame 1)
      - Governor with cousins of daughter in law, Barbara (Roll 826C, Frame 2)
      - Governor visits Boy Scouts exhibit (Roll 826C, Frame 3)
      - Governor with Ross Daniels and his four sons (Roll 826C, Frame 4)
      - Governor with Girl Scouts- Betty Ann Giedd, Karen Offil (Roll 826C, Frame 5)
      - Governor with Fred Sattler (Roll 826C, Frame 6)
      - Governor in crowd at Fair (Roll 826C, Frame 7-10)
      - Governor speaking at Fair (Roll 826C, Frame 11)
      - Close up end of day, Cook tired, etc (Roll 826C, Frame 12)
    - untitled, 35 mm. (Roll 826D)
    - Governor at Duchess County Republican Booth at Fair (Roll 826D, Frame 22-24)
    - Governor speaks at Duchess County Fair (Roll 826D, Frame 25)
  - Jones Beach, Long Island, NY, 1966 August 27 (Box 7)
    - Roll 827A, 1008.15/Roll827A; (10) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827B, 1008.15/Roll827B; (10) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827C, 1008.15/Roll827C; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827D, 1008.15/Roll827D; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827E, 1008.15/Roll827E; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827F, 1008.15/Roll827F; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827G, 1008.15/Roll827G; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827H, 1008.15/Roll827H; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827I, 1008.15/Roll827I; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827J, 1008.12/Roll827J; (11) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827K, 1008.15/Roll827K; (2) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827L, 1008.15/Roll827L; (8) (Box 7)
    - Roll 827M, 1008.15/Roll827M; (12) (Box 7)
  - New York City, 1966 August 29-30; 1008.15/Roll829A-F, 830A-E (Box 7)
    - State Narcotic Control Commission. Governor with members of the Commission: L to R: Dr. Henry Bill, Lawrence W. Pierce (Chairman), Governor, Weldon H. Smith (new member), Arthur J Rogers, Santiago Grevi. (Box 7)
      - Governor with Chairman Lawrence W. Pierce and Weldon H. Smith at Press Conference (Box 7)
    - Governor at Educational Alliance (Roll 829B)
    - Governor with bearded man at newspaper offices (Roll 829B)
    - Governor at 84 Clinton St. store front (Roll 829C)
    - At Clinton St Store Opening (Roll 829, Frame 1)
    - Tape cutting and manager wife and child at Union Square rally (Roll 829, Frame 2)
    - at 151 East 116th St. Store Front (Roll 829E)
      - Governor arrives at store front (Roll 829E, Frame 1)
      - Governor with young Republican group (Roll 829E, Frame 2)
      - Governor speaking (Roll 829E, Frame 3)
      - Governor cuts tape (Roll 829E, Frame 4-5)
      - Governor and Attorney General at buffet and with supporter inside store (Roll 829E, Frame 6-7)
      - Governor with Mrs. Catherine Irizarry, a missionary working at St. Anthony's Mission (Roll 829E, Frame 8-9)
      - Arriving at 72nd and Broadway (Roll 829E, Frame 10)
      - Store Front (Roll 829E, Frame 11)
    - Governor at 2080 Broadway Storefront (Roll 829F)
    - Governor at 15 Charles Street Storefront (Roll 829F)
    - Governor with Navel and Marine Corps officers as he read proclamations and received stamp celebrating 50th Anniv. of Marine Corps Reserve (Roll 830A)
    - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller at Suffolk County Republican Convention Club at Hotel Plaza, NY (Roll 830B)
      - Left to Right - Burning of Republican Headquarters Mortgage, Governor Rockefeller, Mrs. Rockefeller, Atty. Gen. Samuel Lebowitz, county Leader Robert Curcio of Suffolk County (Roll 830B, Frame 5-8)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller with Robert Curcio of Suffolk County (Roll 830B, Frame 9)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller (Roll 830B, Frame 10-11)
      - Governor with Mrs. Ervine A. Gaggin wife of Rep. Leader of Lyndenhurst, LI (Roll 830B, Frame 12)
    - Governor with Robert Curcie, Mrs. Rockefeller at right (Roll 830C, Frame 1)
    - Governor speaks at dinner (Roll 830C, Frame 2)
    - At Press Reception - Franks Restaurant, 315 West 125th St, Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller at Reception (Roll 830C, Frame 3-12)
    - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller at Press Reception (Roll 830D, Frame 1-12)
    - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller at Press Reception (Roll 830E, Frame 1-4)
  - Warrensburg, NY, 1966 August 31; 1008.15/Roll831A; (10) (Box 7)
    - Governor and scenes of the opening ceremonies of 18 1/2 miles of the Adirondack Northway (Roll 831A)
      - Governor arrives (Roll 831A, Frame 1-2)
      - View of ceremonies (Roll 831A, Frame 3-6)
  - Diamond Point, NY, 1008.15/Roll831B; (10) (Box 7)
    - Governor with Mrs. Sylvia Putnam (Diamond Point NY) (Roll 831B, Frame 1)
    - At Spectacular - Hamilton County (Roll 831B)
    - Governor drives 1929 Rolls Royce, the owner: Robert McVoy, Poland NY is also in front seat (Roll 831B)
    - Governor speaking at Speculator Rally (Roll 831B)
  - Speculator. NY, 1008.15/Roll831C; (11) (Box 7)
    - Governor with Mrs. Stella King, of Speculator NY, who presented book to Governor (Roll 831C, Frame 1)
    - Governor meets members of Ukranian Girl Scout troop (Roll 831C, Frame 2-4)
      At Speculator Governor with two women with small youngsters left - Mrs. Jane Kresmery; right - Mrs. Ethel Hoegemann.
  - Syracuse. NY, 1008.15/Roll83ID-831E; (12) (Box 7)
    - Governor with Vincent Keenan (of Syracuse. NY) (Roll 831D, Frame 1)
    - Governor with Major Walksh of Syracuse and Carmine Basilio (Roll 831D, Frame 2)
    - Governor speaking to Syracuse Labor leaders (Roll 831D, Frame 3-5)
    - Governor with Dick Vaccaro (Syracuse NY) (labor leaders) (Roll 831D, Frame 6-7)
    - Governor with William S Quinn (labor leaders) (Roll 831D, Frame 8)
    - Governor with various labor leaders (Roll 831D, Frame 9-12)
    - Governor with labor leaders at Syracuse (Roll 831E, Frame 1-4)
    - Governor at Farm Bureau Dinner at Syracuse (Roll 831E, Frame 5-7)
    - Governor with various County Dairy Princess (Roll 831E, Frame 5-7)
    - Pix of Labor Leaders - sufficient for all in photos to: Bob Gormley, Campaign HQs (Roll 831E)
    - Governor rides helicopter to cut ribbon and inspect the new section of Route 87 at Warrensburg, NY (Roll 831)
  - Warrensburg. NY, 1008.15/Roll83IF; (13) (Box 7)
  - Red Room. Eugene Glusker, Mayor AmericoDi Francesca, Gordon Cameron. Richard Fritz, John Mulroy, 1966 September 1; 1008.15/1774 - 1008.15/1775 (Box 7)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1966 September 1; 1008.15/Roll91A-91H, 91J (Box 7)
    - Governor with Mr. and Mrs. Albert S Leibs (Syracuse NY) (Roll 91A, Frame 3)
    - Governor with Andy Daniels (of Livonia, NY) (Roll 91A, Frame 4)
    - Governor with Jonathan Vosburgh (RFD Silverlake, Rd.,Pavilion, NY) (Roll 91A, Frame 5)
    - Governor at review of National Guard (Roll 91A, Frame 6)
    - Governor inspects tank. In picture is Warrant Officer C. L. Hagerty (of Whitesboro, NY) (Roll 91A, Frame 7-8)
    - Governor autographs newspaper of George Snell (of Syracuse) (Roll 91A, Frame 9)
    - Governor with 3 members of National Guard, special forces detail: Daniel Curry (Albany) Max Van Winkle (of Schenectady) John Yermal (of Antwerp, NY) (Roll 91A, Frame 10-12)
    - Governor with Craig Ashley (of Syracuse NY) (Roll 91B, Frame 1-3)
    - Governor with Miss Nell Aldredge (of Syracuse, NY) and Mrs. Henry Keen (of Syracuse, NY) (Roll 91B, Frame 4)
    - Governor with Mr. and Mrs. Ha Mason (of DeWitt, NY) (Roll 91C, Frame 3-4)
    - 1966 State Science Congress Awards. Governor with Angela Longo (of Niagara Falls, NY) (Roll 91C, Frame 6-7)
    - Governor with Mark Lichtenstein (of Rosly, NY) (Roll 91C, Frame 8)
    - Governor with Mary Lou Silkworm (of Amityville, NY) (Roll 91C, Frame 9)
    - Governor with Bonnie J. Zimmer (of Newark Valley, NY) (Roll 91C, Frame 10)
    - Governor with Ronald Garson (of New Hyde Pk, NY) (Roll 91C, Frame 11)
    - Governor with 8 y/o John Skevnick, (Ilion, NY) (Roll 91D, Frame 1-2)
    - Mrs. Rockefeller is in some of these negatives (Roll 91D, Frame 3-4)
    - At State Police Exhibit (Box 7)
      - Governor shoots at pistol range (Roll 91E, Frame 1-4)
      - Governor with trooper at exhibit examining pistol. Major J.A. Miller, Sgt. O'Neil (Roll 91E, Frame 5)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller at Fair to greet huge throng (Roll 91E, Frame 7-8)
      - Untitled (Roll 91E, Frame 9-10)
    - untitled (Box 7)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller in crowd at Fair (Roll 91F, Frame 1-7)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller with Mrs (Roll 91F, Frame 8)
      - Governor watches Fred Zauter, Brewerton, NY, operate spinning wheel (Roll 91F, Frame 9)
      - Governor watches 8 y/o Susan Lowe of W. Monroe, operate spinning wheel (Roll 91F, Frame 10-11)
      - Governor at Republican booth (Roll 91F, Frame 12)
      - Governor with Emerson Miller (of Herkimer NY) (Roll 91G, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor rides tractor train (Roll 91G, Frame 3)
      - Governor and Mrs. R. with Michele Kelsey of NY and with bull of C.A. Eccleston of Hamilton NY (not in picture) (Roll 91G, Frame 5-6)
      - Governor & Mrs. R. with Charles Goodwin and his son Carl of Guilford, NY and jersey calf. Charles Goodwin is President of NYS. Purebred Dairy Cattle Committee (Roll 91G, Frame 7-8)
      - Governor and Mrs. R. with grand champion Guernsey cow of Henry C. Veniew of Lafayette NY In picture is Paul C. Fleming (Phelps, NY) (Roll 91G, Frame 9)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller on tractor train (Roll 91G, Frame 10)
      - Governor greets unidentified women as he rides tractor train (Roll 91G, Frame 11)
      - Governor & Mrs. Rockefeller with Mrs. Samuel Lahood (Auburn, NY) and Mrs. Victoria Bruer of Grant Village, NY (Syracuse) (Roll 91H, Frame 1-2)
      - Mrs. Rockefeller with Carol Lockwood of Castile, NY (Beef Queen) (Roll 91H, Frame 4-5)
      - Governor with Kenneth Burr (Trumansburg, NY) with Trophy won by Tompkins County HH Dairy Club (Roll 91H, Frame 6-7)
      - Governor with Mrs. Victor Giorno (left) (Syracuse NY) and Mrs. Carmella Bartolomeo (Camillus NY) (Roll 91H, Frame 8-9)
      - Governor and Don Wickham (Roll 91H, Frame 10)
      - Governor speaking at Fair luncheon (Roll 91H, Frame 11)
      - Governor with Glenn Brown Jr. of Randolph, NY (Roll 91J, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor with Major (Roll 91J, Frame 3)
      - Governor with group of Air Force women recruits at Syracuse Airport. Names to come from Major Pacer, US Air Force Recruiter, Syracuse (Roll 91J, Frame 4-5)
  - Rensselaer County Fair, NY, 1966 September 2; 1008.15/Roll92A-92E (Box 7)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Rensselaer County Fair, Schaghticoke and Chatham. NY, 1966 August 2 (Box 7)
      - Governor with Thomas Brennan, Supervisor 14 Ward Troy and Chairman of 175th Anniversary (Roll 92A, Frame 1)
      - celebration and Neil Kelleher Assembly candidate (Roll 92A, Frame 2)
      - Governor autographs arm cast of Kelly Anne Quinn 5 y/o (Troy NY) her mother Mrs. Ray J Quinn holding her (Roll 92A, Frame 4)
      - Governor with Diane Shutter of Main St. Schaghticoke (Roll 92A, Frame 6)
      - Governor speaking at Fair Grounds (Roll 92A, Frame 7-8)